vreecase.com 2017-10-02

# Privacy Policy

##  Privacy Policy 

**1\. What Do We Do with Your Information?**  
We'll collect the personal information you gave us including name and email address when you addpoints. Steam profiles are used for identification purposes across the site. The Service provider collects a small piece of information sent from browser (cookies) which might be turned off. However, turning off cookies may restrict the use of the Site. By accepting the Terms, you consent to the Service provider informing you from time to time about changes on the Site, new services and promotions.

**2\. Security**  
By using the Site you acknowledge and consent to the Service provider processing your personal data for the purposes of allowing access and usage of the Site and in order to allow participating in activities provided at the Site. Your personal data will not be disclosed to any third parties, unless such disclosure is necessary for processing your requests, to carry verification procedures or unless it is required by law. You have the right to access personal data held by the Service provider about you. You hereby consent and undertake to immediately inform the Service provider about changes of the personal data or other provided information.

**3\. Items and association**  
Don't attempt to bypass any trade filters. You can't add manipulated skins prices or your withdraw option will be restricted and points taken away. You can not trade skins on the site. Vreecase is not affiliated with Valve Corporation or Steam.

**4\. Points**  
If you keep points without using them for over 30 days, your points will be removed in virtue of inactivity. You must gamble at least 50% of your points amount to withdraw. This rule is only for players, not referrers.

**5\. Age Of Consent**  
By scanning on the site, you have acknowledged that you are 18 years or more. If you do not agree with it or you are under 18, then immediately withdraw all the points from your account and do not continue the game.

**6\. Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarification will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances.

**7\. Questions**  
If you have any questions, contact us at support#vreecase.com (replace "#" to "@").
